atsondemand.com 2016-05-28

# Privacy | ATS OnDemand

**Privacy**

**Effective Date: 10/21/2015**

**ATS OnDemand Privacy Statement**

Outer Limits Technology, Inc., dba ATS OnDemand is committed to honoring the privacy of our users. We strive to provide a safe, secure user experience. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to our [https://power.atsondemand.com](https://power.atsondemand.com/) (“Web site”). By using the Web site, you consent to the policies and practices described in this Statement.

Your data will be stored and processed in whole in the United States. If you access the Website outside the United States, your usage of that site constitutes consent to the transfer of your data out of your country and to the United States. This statement discloses the privacy practices that apply to the online collection of data on [https://power.atsondemand.com](https://power.atsondemand.com/) owned and operated by Outer Limits Technology, Inc., dba ATS OnDemand.

**TRUSTe Privacy Program**

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through our website, [https://power.atsondemand.com](https://power.atsondemand.com/) and does not cover information collected behind the log in on our website. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. In order to view our relationship with TRUSTe, please visit the validation page visible by clicking on the TRUSTe seal. If you have unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Outer Limits Technology, Inc., dba ATS OnDemand complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. – Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Outer Limits Technology, Inc., dba ATS OnDemand has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Outer Limits Technology, Inc., dba ATS OnDemand’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

* * *

**Information that is gathered on the Web site**

ATS OnDemand will not sell, share, or rent any customer information that is contained on the site. We do not share any information with third parties for any reason including marketing.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information  _only as necessary to provide_ _ _ these services to us.

**How Personal Information is Collected and Used**

You can visit the ATS OnDemand website without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. We collect no such information about you, unless you choose to provide that information to us.

If you choose to provide your data, it will be stored and processed in whole in the United States. If you access the ATS OnDemand Website outside the United States, your usage of that site constitutes consent to the transfer of your data out of your country and to the United States. This statement discloses the privacy practices that apply to the online collection of data obtained on [https://power.atsondemand.com](http://www.power.atsondemand.com/), owned and operated by Outer Limits Technology, Inc. dba ATS OnDemand.

**Information that is gathered from Registration Forms**

ATS OnDemand gathers contact information (such as name, address, email address, phone number) from certain registration, contact us requests, email-a-friend, resume submission, and seminar forms. The contact information that is gathered is for the sole purpose of corresponding with the parties that have expressed interest in the ATS OnDemand products or seminars. Based on the type of request made, ATS OnDemand website will acknowledge your submission and a ATS OnDemand representative will respond via telephone with requested product or seminar information.

**Email a Friend**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about a job opening listed on our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. An email will be sent from you to your friend. ATS OnDemand does not store this information except for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

**Choice/Opt-out**

If you do not wish to be contacted by ATS OnDemand, please do not enter any contact information on the site. All communications from the site may be critical service updates or telephone or email responses to inquiries or services that you have requested. If you are contacted by ATS OnDemand and do not wish to be contacted again, please indicate so in your response email or contact us at [info@atsondemand.com](mailto:info@atsondemand.com).

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

At any time, ATS OnDemand provides you an opportunity to correct, change, or delete your personally identifiable information. Such changes can be made by contacting ATS OnDemand at [info@atsondemand.com](mailto:info@atsondemand.com). Any access request will be responded to within 30 days of submission.

Also, you may contact [info@atsondemand.com](mailto:info@atsondemand.com) to access or delete your information submitted to us on any form on the site. If you have a ATS OnDemand account, you may also contact your internal System Administrator to change, delete, or deactivate your account.

**Tracking Technologies**

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Pereless Systems and our partners such as Google analytics to review trends and sourcing for jobs that the candidates apply to. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our job cart, to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference, job applied, apply steps, and authentication).  Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

**Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

**Email links on the Website**

The ATS OnDemand Website contains links for users to contact us directly. We use the information provided to respond directly to any issues, comments or requests for information. In some cases we may store your comments in order to improve the system.

**Links to 3rd Party Sites**

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of ATS OnDemand. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

**Social Media Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.

**Security**

ATS OnDemand has implemented reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected as stated above both online and off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative or sales representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [info@atsondemand.com](mailto:info@atsondemand.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this statement, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**We welcome your comments concerning this Privacy Statement**

Contact Information:

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy statement, please contact us at: [website-feedback@atsondemand.com](mailto:website-feedback@atsondemand.com)

Outer Limits Technology, Inc

151 Bodman Place

Red Bank, NJ 07701
